Young Madam.
How dare you!
Just wait.
I'll go report to the Madam.
Thank you, Young Madam.
Xue.
It's okay.
Ms. Ling
copied these for you.
Copy some more,
and put them inside.
No one will notice.
Xueqiu,
you're really a good girl.
Miss Xueqiu seems to go out a lot lately.
Have you ever been in love?
What
is love?
It's
dating a man.
No.
Men
are not good.
Xueqiu
Qingyou, help me.
I don't want to marry Ye Wenbo.
My grandma insists on marrying me to him.
That playboy, in order to marry into our family,
regardless of his daughter's young age,
beat his wife to death.
My grandma is pushing me into the fire.
They
They are coming soon.
Let's hide here.
Why are there so many people?
Did you hide Xueqiu?
Where did you hide her?
Grandma,
the floor is old and unattended,
so it makes noise.
I have important matters to deal with,
so I'll leave you alone.
Please.
Let's go.
Xueqiu.
Qingyou.
It's okay.
Your brother
loves you.
Qingyou, save me.
Young Marshal, you came back.
Is it because he's afraid that I'll take Xueqiu away
and ruin the marriage between Ye and Ling families?
The Ye family's young master is a bit frivolous,
but as long as I'm here,
he won't hurt Xueqiu.
Moreover, this matter
concerns the business of the Ling family,
it's not a trivial matter.
Using your sister's marriage
to exchange for business,
you're really a decent Young Marshal.
If you really want to protect her,
you should break off the engagement,
instead of pushing her into a pit of fire.
Don't provoke me, my lady.
This is the business of the Ling family.
It's not your turn to interfere.
Xueqiu,
I don't want to marry that playboy of the Ye family.
If you want to marry,
then marry my dead body.
Nonsense!
Punishing yourself for someone else's mistake,
what kind of sense does that make?
Qingming,
I...
I'll go find Huai.
I'll elope with him.
I...
I'll beat the love-struck out of you!
Your engagement is known to all.
If he really cares about you,
he would've done something.
How can you
settle for being a concubine
when you're the head of the Ling family?
Enough!
Give me the gun.
You'll reflect
in the ancestral hall today.
You have two days to decide
if you'll accept this marriage
or
I'll announce to the public
that Miss Ling is disobedient
and will never get married,
and end the Ye family's hope.
Lock the door.
Yes.
Brother,
someone's coming.
Miss, this is your lunch.
OK.
I'll take you out.
Come on.
Xueqiu.
You got out of here.
The rest of the way,
you have to go by yourself.
Your Highness.
I can't repay
your great kindness.
Xueqiu...
I can only repay it in the next life.
What are you talking about?
Before they find us,
hurry up.
Run that way.
Hurry up.
You, Su Muwan,
you must be the one who hit my head.
Last time, you hit my head,
and you stopped Ling Xueqiu from marrying me.
Are you okay?
How dare you ruin my good thing.
Watch out!
Su Muwan.
Doctor,
how is she?
Her wound has turned black.
The dagger must be poisoned.
The poison
is very strong.
So the most important thing now
is to detoxify her body
first.
You're awake.
The fever is gone.
Xueqiu...
Is she...
Don't worry.
No one can force my sister
into marriage.
You've been here all along?
Yes.
Don't
do anything like that again.
What do you mean?
Blocking a knife?
It's the stupidest thing.
If it happens again,
I'll do the same.
Take a nap.
You're still weak.
I can only sleep soundly
when you're here.
I disagree with this marriage.